https://hotspotsmagazine.com/2011/01/01/privacy-policy/

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
HS Live
Watch! Hotspots LIVE! | Oct 27th, 2020 | LGBTQ+ Democratic Vote…
Your Personal Information is Safe
We support the rights of adults to explore entertainment and sexuality on the Internet in a private and secure environment. As a visitor of  & HotSpotsMagazine.com, you will have peace-of-mind knowing that any information you share privately with us will be kept strictly confidential. This includes, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, address, phone number, or personal information regarding the use of this site. If information is collected from you, the information will only be used to provide the products and services you’ve requested, to provide customer service, or to share news about our service offerings.
Your e-mail address and personal information will never be sold to 3rd parties for marketing purposes, and will only be transferred to other entities should the  & HotSpotsMagazine.com website change ownership. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us via our on-site contact form.
Please note that any information you publicly reveal in our community forums, comment areas or in public chat does not fall under the above policy. This policy applies only to personally identifiable information you share privately with the operators of  & HotSpotsMagazine.com.Cookie Policy
We use cookies to help remember you as you surf HotSpotsMagazine.com. These cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information and help enhance your usage of the site. Without them, you may not be able to fully enjoy many aspects of the site such as staying logged in while using our services.
————————
By entering this web site you are making the following statements:
1. Under penalty of perjury, I swear/affirm that as of this moment, I am at least 18 years of age.
2. Each adult person who enters as well as applies for membership is bound by the specific laws that govern their own countries, states and communities. By proceeding forth you acknowledge and agree to full and complete responsibilities, liabilities and accountabilities for any such violations and release this web site from such.
3. I am not accessing this material to use it against the site operator, or any other person whomsoever, in any conceivable manner.
4. If I use the service of this site in violation of the above agreement, I understand I may be in violation of both local and federal laws.
————————
Limited License (Use of Service): HotSpotsMagazine.com provides the materials on this site for personal, non-commercial use by viewers, guests, visitors, and members of this website. Users are granted a single copy license to download or print each file and/or page made available for downloading found on this site for personal, non-commercial use only. HotSpotsMagazine.com reserves the right to limit the amount of materials downloaded.
Users may not: use any of the materials found in any area of this website for any commercial public display, performance, sale or rental; remove, modify or alter any copyright or other proprietary notice, or trademarks from any of the materials found in any area of this website; or otherwise transfer any material located in any area of this website to any other person or entity.
If at any time you breach or violate any provision of this User Agreement, HotSpotsMagazine.com reserves the right to terminate this license.
You agree to hold HotSpotsMagazine.com, and its staff, subsidiaries, and affiliates, harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of content you submit, post, transmit or make available through the service, your use of the service, your connection to the service, your violation of the User Agreement, or your violation of any rights of another.
————————
Disclaimer: Your use of the service is at your sole risk. The materials on this website are provided “as is” without any express or implied warranty of any kind including warranties of merchantability, no infringement of intellectual property or fitness for a particular purpose. HotSpotsMagazine.com offers no assurance of uninterrupted or error-free service. this website does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the information, text, graphics, links or other items contained on this web site. HotSpotsMagazine.com may change any of the information found at this site at any time without notice. HotSpotsMagazine.com makes no commitment to update the information found at this site. HotSpotsMagazine.com shall not be liable for any damages arising out of the use or inability to use the material or information available on this site.
Any material downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of the service is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any damage to your computer system or loss of data that results from the download of any such material.
HotSpotsMagazine.com shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible losses (even if HotSpotsMagazine.com has been advised of the possibility of such damages), resulting from: the use or the inability to use the service; the cost of procurement of substitute goods and services resulting from any goods, data, information or services purchased or obtained or messages received or transactions entered into through or from the service; unauthorized access to or alteration of your transmissions or data; statements or conduct of any third party on the service; or any other matter relating to the service.
HotSpotsMagazine.com reserves the right at any time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. HotSpotsMagazine.com shall not be liable to you for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the service.
Your access to HotSpotsMagazine.com files is a privilege, not a right. If HotSpotsMagazine.com deems that your access is inconsistent with the goals of this website, your access may be temporarily or permanently restricted or blocked. If HotSpotsMagazine.com believes that you have violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit of the User Agreement, HotSpotsMagazine.com, in its sole discretion, may terminate your access or use of the service, or any part thereof, for any reason.
————————
Public Communication Areas, User Weblogs(blogs), Guestbook’s, Chat rooms, and Message Boards are publicly accessible to anyone on the internet. Public posts transmitted and uploaded by users to such pages may be accessible to the general public. User posts are not pre-screened before posting. They are automatically posted. HotSpotsMagazine.com reserves the right (but not the obligation) to edit or delete posts. HotSpotsMagazine.com does not control the content posted via the service and, as such, does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such content. HotSpotsMagazine.com disclaims any liability with respect to content in the public communication areas.
All information, files, data, text, photographs, graphics, video, messages or other materials (“content”), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, are the sole responsibility of the person from which such content originated. You, not HotSpotsMagazine.com, are entirely responsible for all content that you upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available via the service. Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding your online conduct and acceptable content.
You agree not to post infringing, defamatory, libelous or otherwise unlawful material, or any material deemed excessively violent, harassing, threatening or otherwise objectionable. It is HotSpotsMagazine.com’s right, but not obligation, to monitor, delete and/or modify such posts and/or report such posts to legal authorities. If you are aware of any such material posted on this site, please contact HotSpotsMagazine.com
————————
Links to other web sites found on HotSpotsMagazine.com are controlled by third parties. Those linked sites are not under the control of HotSpotsMagazine.com, and HotSpotsMagazine.com is not responsible for the content or policies of any linked site or any link contained in a link site.
HotSpotsMagazine.com provides those links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by HotSpotsMagazine.com of any linked site.
Your correspondence or business dealings with, or participation in promotions of, advertisers found on or through the service, including payment and delivery of related goods or services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings, are solely between you and such advertiser.
HotSpotsMagazine.com shall not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings or as the result of the presence of such advertisers on the service.
RELATED ARTICLESMORE FROM AUTHOR
Uncategorized
Deep Inside Hollywood
HS Live
Watch! Hotspots Live! | Creative Ideas For You At Home
Features
Hotspot Hotties
Uncategorized
Georgies Alibi Monkey Bar_ 10th annual Grateful Paws benefit
Please enter your comment!
ABOUT USHotspots - Mark's List - Genre Latino
Proud to be Florida's Largest LGBT Media Network.
© Hotspots Media Group - Copyright 2019 - By 7Elements Web Design
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. Yes, I accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
